Links: [California Privacy Additional Information](#californiaprivacystatement)  |  [General Privacy Statement](#privacystatement)

#### **PLEASE NOTE: We DO NOT have information on or collect your: name, address, phone number, or know your personal identity.**

* * *

Privacy Policy

* * *

Our Policy Effective Date: December 31, 2022 Enotem, Inc., operating the Emergency Email & Wireless Network, (�we� or the �Company�) uses its best efforts to respect the privacy of its subscribers and online visitors. This policy explains what personal information we collect on our website (https://www.emergencyemail.org/), when you subscribe to or use our services, or through other means, and how we use and share that information. This policy may change from time to time. When we revise this Privacy Policy, we will update the effective date listed above. Your continued use of our services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the Privacy Policy periodically for updates. If you are a resident of California, Nevada, or Virginia, there are additional sections of this Privacy Policy that apply to you. **Information We Collect** We collect information about you when you subscribe to our services including from co-registration partners, and automatically as you navigate our website or receive or engage with our emails or alerts. Contact information: Such as your email Location information: Such as the zip code of your choice that you supply Technical information: Such as how often you interact with the information we send you, the Internet Protocol address assigned to you by your Internet service provider, or a unique personal identifier that is assigned. We also collect information from third parties to aid in conducting our business. As further described under �Cookies� below, our third-party advertising partners may use cookies and other similar technologies to recognize you and/or your device(s) and collect information about your interactions on or across different websites, services, and devices. **How We Use Your Personal Information** We use the information you submit or we collect about you for a variety of purposes relating to our services. More specifically, we may use your information to: Provide you our services Respond to you about our website and services, including to unsubscribe you from our email or alert service Communicate with you about your account or subscriptions, including to offer other services Notify you about changes to our services Improve our services Enable third parties to provide advertising to you Third parties may also use information collected from you to provide you with targeted advertising. **How We Disclose Your Information** We may disclose your information for the purposes listed above with: Vendors or third-party service providers that support us in providing services. Third parties providing advertising or analytic services. Law enforcement or regulatory agencies, if required to do so by law or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate. Other entities in connection with the sale, merger, acquisition or other reorganization of our organization. As otherwise permitted by applicable law. Further Information on �Cookies� Visitors should be aware that information may be automatically collected by us and by third party advertising partners in connection with our website and email services through the use of �cookies,� for the purposes listed above. �Cookies� are small text files that can be used to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor�s ongoing access to and use of the site, and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor�s system and damage files. Our advertising partners also use third-party cookies, which may be used to collect personal information and deliver targeted advertising to you. You may opt out of the use of other types of cookies (except strictly necessary cookies which are needed for the website to operate) by modifying your browser setting to decline cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block certain cookies you may not be able to access all or parts of our Services. Children�s Information Our website and services are not directed toward children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from children under the age of 13. Links to Other Websites Our website or services may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these linked websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these sites before providing any personal information. Security We have taken appropriate security measures to safeguard your information by implementing reasonable technical and physical security measures based on the type of data we process. Do Not Track Our website does not respond to Do Not Track signals.

#### Additional Information for California Residents: Notice at Collection, and Notice of Right to Opt-Out

Effective Date: December 31, 2022 This section of the Privacy Policy only applies to residents of California. Terms that are capitalized are defined in the California law. We provide this Notice at Collection and Personal Information Rights for California Residents (the �CCPA Privacy Notice�) to supplement the information contained in the general Privacy Policy above. This CCPA Privacy Notice describes the Personal Information we may have collected directly from you or indirectly about you if you use our website or services, and how we have used and/or disclosed your Personal Information, as required by the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, as amended by the Consumer Privacy Rights Act of 2020, (collectively the �CCPA�), including the Personal Information collected about Consumers in the preceding 12 months and Personal Information that will be collected about Consumers. The CCPA Privacy Notice applies only to individuals residing in the State of California who are considered �Consumers� under the CCPA and from whom we collect �Personal Information� as described in the CCPA (�Consumers�). For additional details about privacy, please see the other sections of our [general privacy policy](#privacystatement).  
  
Categories and Examples of Personal Information Collected We may collect Personal Information about you in a variety of different situations, including, but not limited to when you use our website, subscribe to or use our services, or through other means of collecting data. More specifically, we collect the following categories of Personal Information from Consumers: Identifiers:�Such as email address and IP address Internet or other similar network activity: Such as information regarding a consumer�s interaction with an internet website application Geolocation data: Zip code information Sensitive data: We do not collect sensitive data. As further described under �Cookies� above, our third-party advertising partners may use cookies and other similar technologies to recognize you and/or your device(s) and collect information about your interactions on or across different websites, services, and devices. Categories of Sources of Personal Information Directly from you. We collect Personal Information when you engage with our website or services. Indirectly from you, including via third parties. We collect Personal Information from co-registration partners, and automatically as you navigate our website or receive or engage with our emails or alerts, including from analytics partners. Purposes for Collecting Personal Information We may collect Personal Information for the business or commercial purposes listed under [How We Use Your Personal Information](#howweuse) in the general Privacy Policy. Personal Information Disclosed for Business Purposes Categories of Entities to Whom We Disclose Personal Information for a Business Purpose. We may disclose your Personal Information for a business purpose, including to our service providers and advertising partners. For more information, see the section [How We Disclose Your Information](#howwedisclose) above. Categories of Personal Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose. Identifiers:�Such as email address and IP address Internet or other similar network activity: Such as information regarding a consumer�s interaction with an internet website application Geolocation data:�Physical location, such as zip code �Selling� and �Sharing� Personal Information As defined by the CCPA, we may Sell and Share certain online identifiers for the purposes of online advertising and analytics. We do not have actual knowledge that we Sell or Share Personal Information about consumers under 16 years of age. You have the right to opt-out of Selling and Sharing. For more information about these activities and to exercise your right to opt-out of Selling and Sharing, please see our [�Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information� page](https://www.emergencyemail.org/privacyrequestcontact.asp). Retention We retain Personal Information as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill business purposes, achieve other purposes for which it was collected, and for compliance with legal obligations or requests. Your CCPA Consumer Rights The CCPA provides Consumers with specific rights regarding their Personal Information. This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights. The right to know what Personal Information the business has collected about the consumer, including the categories of Personal Information, the categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing Personal Information, the categories of third parties to whom the business discloses Personal Information, and the specific pieces of Personal Information the business has collected about the consumer; The right to delete Personal Information that the business has collected from the consumer, subject to certain exceptions; The right to correct inaccurate Personal Information that a business maintains about a consumer; The right to opt-out of the sale or sharing of Personal Information by the business�for more information, please visit our [�Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information� page](https://www.emergencyemail.org/privacyrequestcontact.asp); If the business uses or discloses Sensitive Personal Information for certain reasons, the right to limit the use or disclosure of sensitive Personal Information by the business; however, we do not use or disclose Sensitive Personal Information in a way that would trigger this right; and The right not to receive discriminatory treatment by the business for the exercise of privacy rights conferred by the CCPA. Exercising Your CCPA Rights To exercise your right to opt-out, please see our [�Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information� page](https://www.emergencyemail.org/privacyrequestcontact.asp)page. Alternatively, you can exercise your consumer rights by emailing us at support at emergencyemail.org. Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your Personal Information. The verifiable consumer request must: Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected Personal Information or an authorized representative. Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it. You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Information relates to you. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us. We will only use Personal Information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor�s identity or authority to make the request. CCPA Response Timing and Format We try to respond to a verifiable consumer request within forty-five (45) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. If you have an account with us, we will deliver our written response to that account. If you do not have an account with us, we will deliver our written response by mail or electronically, at your option. The response we provide will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request. Changes to Our CCPA Privacy Notice We reserve the right to amend this privacy notice at our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this privacy notice, we will post the updated notice on our website and update the notice�s Effective Date above.�Your continued use of our Sites or interaction with us through other methods following the posting of changes and/or our directing you to the updated CCPA Privacy Notice constitutes your acceptance of such changes. California Contact Information To contact us for questions about our privacy policies, email us at support at emergencyemail.org.

#### Additional Information for Nevada�Residents

This section of the Privacy Policy only applies to residents of Nevada. If you are not a resident of Nevada, this section does not apply to you. Terms that are capitalized are defined in the Nevada law. As defined under Nevada law, we do not engage in any Sales of Covered Information. However, Nevada Consumers may submit a verified request at any time directing that we not make any Sale of any Covered Information that we have collected or will collect about the Consumer, as defined under the Nevada law. To submit such a request, you can email support at emergencyemail.org.

#### Additional Information for Virginia�Residents

This section of the Privacy Policy only applies to residents of Virginia. Terms that are capitalized are defined in the Virginia law. Pursuant Virginia�s Consumer Data Protection Act, as amended (�VCDPA�), Virginia residents have certain data privacy rights. This section describes the Personal Data we may have collected directly from you or indirectly about you if you use our sites and/or services and how we have used and/or disclosed your Personal Data. It also describes your rights under the VCDPA. Categories of Personal Data Processed: Please see [Information We Collect](#informationwecollect) in our general Privacy Policy. Purposes for which Personal Data Is Collected: Please see [How We Use Your Information](#howweuse) in our general Privacy Policy, which describes the business or commercial purposes for which your Personal Data may be used. Categories of Personal Data Shared with Third Parties, and Categories of Third Parties with Whom Personal Data Is Shared: See [How We Disclose Your Information](#howwedisclose) in our general Privacy Policy, which describes the third parties with whom we may disclose your Personal Data. This may apply to each category of Personal Data we disclose. Targeted Advertising: We process personal data for third parties to engage in Targeted Advertising. Virginia residents have the right to opt-out of this processing. To exercise your right to opt-out, please see our [�Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information� page.](https://www.emergencyemail.org/privacyrequestcontact.asp) Your Virginia Rights: If you are a resident of Virginia, you have the following rights: To confirm whether or not we are processing your personal data and to access such personal data; To correct inaccuracies in your personal data; To delete your personal data; To obtain a copy of your personal data that you have previously provided to us; and To opt-out of targeted advertising, the sale of personal data, or automated profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you. How Virginia Residents Can Exercise Your Virginia Rights: If you are a resident of Virginia: To exercise your right to opt out, please see our [�Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information� page](https://www.emergencyemail.org/privacyrequestcontact.asp). We will work to verify your request using reasonable means, but, if we are unable to do so, we may ask you follow-up questions. To protect your Personal Data, when submitting your request, please provide information sufficient for us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal data and describe your request with sufficient detail. We will process your verifiable request free of charge, but we are only obligated to provide information to you pursuant to such requests two times in a 12-month period. We may deny your request in whole or in part if we cannot verify your identity. Under the VCDPA, you may appeal our decision regarding your request. If you would like to appeal, please send an email to support at emergencyemail.org, with the word �Appeal� in the subject line.

* * *

Privacy Statement

* * *

**Our Policy**  
The Emergency Email & Wireless Network uses its best efforts to respect the privacy of its online visitors. At our site, we do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not require you to register or provide information to us in order to view our web site.

The Emergency Email & Wireless Network only gathers personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by a visitor directly or through our sponsors. For example, personally identifiable information may be collected in order to respond to a stated desire to receive information from The Emergency Email & Wireless Network. This information is used solely by The Emergency Email & Wireless Network or other entities who are involved in the operation of this site for internal purposes. We will only share personally identifiable information with third parties when the person submitting the information authorizes us to share it or we are required to by law. We may from time contact our lists to offer other services or to identify our sponsors. 

**Is Credit Card Information Secure?**  
We care about the safety and security of your transaction. We use high grade encryption and the https security protocol to communicate with your browser software. This method is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card information you send to us.

**How Do We Use "Cookies"?**  
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected by the Emergency Email & Wireless Network’ Website through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a Website can use to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor’s ongoing access to and use of the site, and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor’s system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature. The Emergency Email & Wireless Network uses "cookie" technology only to obtain non-personal information from its online visitors in order to improve visitors’ online experience and facilitate their visit within our site.

**Note to Parents on Our Privacy Policy**  
The Emergency Email & Wireless Network welcomes children to learn more about our organization and our programs. However, we encourage this to be done only with their parent's knowledge and supervision. For this reason, The Emergency Email & Wirless Network follows the guidelines for interactive electronic media published by the Children’s Advertising Review Unit of the Better Business Bureau. Special notices urging children to get their parent's permission before providing any personal information have been incorporated into our site.

For information about The Emergency Email & Wireless Network and its mission, or to learn about legal or technical issues regarding the use of this site, you can contact us by [clicking here](https://www.emergencyemail.org/govtcontact.asp).

* * *

These privacy policies may change from time to time and apply to emergencyemail.org, The Emergency Email & Wireless Network, an Enotem, Inc. company.
